A prophecy written in blood.
The Last Son is a western, action, adventure film directed by Tim Sutton.
Isaac LeMay, a murderous outlaw, learns he is cursed by a
prophecy: one of his children will kill him.
To prevent this, he hunts down each of his estranged
children, including long-lost son Cal.
With bounty hunters and Sheriff Solomon on his tail, LeMay must
find a way to stop his children and end the curse.
Isaac LeMay, played by Sam Worthington.
Cal, played by mgk.
Soloman, played by Thomas Jane.
Anna, played by Heather Graham.
Megan, played by Emily Marie Palmer.
Grace, played by Kim DeLonghi.
The Last Duel is a 2021 epic historical drama film directed by Ridley Scott from a screenplay by Nicole Holofcener, Ben Affleck, and Matt
Damon, based on the 2004 book The Last Duel: A True Story of Crime, Scandal, and Trial by Combat in Medieval France by Eric Jager.
Set in 14th century France, the film stars Damon as Jean de Carrouges, a knight who challenges his former friend, squire Jacques le
Gris (Adam Driver), to a judicial duel after Jean's wife, Marguerite (Jodie Comer), accuses Jacques of raping her.
The events leading up to the duel are divided into three distinct chapters,
reflecting the contradictory perspectives of the three main characters.
Affleck also stars in a supporting role as Count Pierre d'Alençon.
An adaptation of Jager's book was first announced in 2015, though
it was not officially greenlit until July 2019.
Affleck and Damon were confirmed as stars and co-writers that month,
with Comer and Driver joining the cast later that year.
Filming took place in France and Ireland from February to October 2020,
with a hiatus of several months due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The Last Duel premiered at the 78th Venice International Film Festival on September 10, 2021, and was
theatrically released in the United States on October 15, 2021, by 20th Century Studios.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, and was selected by
the National Board of Review as one of the top ten films of 2021.
Although the film performed poorly at the worldwide box office, it
later found financial success in post-theatrical markets.
The film explores themes of montana, outlaw, evil.
The tone is emotional.